

# JENNIFER BUNNER

# TECHNICAL KNOWLEDGE

Html & Css/Sass/Scss Javascript React.js, Vue.js Quasar Node.js Express.js, npm

jQuery, MVC Graphic design & UX-design PHP, Wordpress

Databases:

Scrum

MySql, noSQL, sql, crud Firebase, Firestore AJAX, JSON, REST Api, Github, Git Visual Studio Code Figma, Zeplin, Agila metoder,

# LANGUAGE SKILLS

Svenska -moder tongue Engelska - fluent Franska - light conversation Spanska - light conversation

## CONTACT

Email bunner.jennifer@gmail.com

Telefonnummer 0735 122431

linkedin.com/in/jenniferbunner810 github.com/iths-jennifer-bunner

## **ABOUT ME**

After many years in the trade and as a Visual Merchandiser, I have now got my degree in frontend development at the IT-Högskolan.

With knowledge such as teamwork, problem solving and communication as well as an eye for detail, I am used to working at a fast pace and stressful situations. I am flexible and like to come along and try new ideas.

My goal is to be able to work as a front-end developer after my degree. My portfolio page: https://www.jenniferbunner.com/

# **EDUCATION**

**IT HÖGSKOLAN 2019-2021** 

Frontend developer. See Technical Knowledge to see what I have studied.

### INTERNSHIP 2

**ZIGNSEC V6-20 2021** 

I was commissioned to make a new portal with improved UI, than the existing one written in Angular, with the aim that the new portal will start to be used on their new platform, I have together with another student designed mockups to code the portal in React.js, Sass, and material.ui. We worked towards an API on their existing database to retrieve information

### INTERNSHIP 1

#### EVIDENT (HTTPS://EVIDENT.CAPITAL/) V34-41 2020

A startup in the fintech industry. Where I had the main responsibility for making their marketing page (from design to deployment). Available at: https://bocapital.se/ I have designed the page in figma and then coded it in vue.js using Quasar framework and Sass / scss. Have translated it using i18n and installed mailchimp.



# JENNIFER BUNNER

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **GINA TRICOT**

#### Visual merchandiser 100406-ongoing

Responsible for Gina tricot's concept being visualized and optimized in the store. Store windows (styling, decoration), styling mannequins, campaign follow-up, placement of goods and work with different surfaces in the store, work with purchase proposals, follow-up of sales and make sure the right product is in the right place, inform staff about our campaigns and trends. Helped to open new stores and at new openings.

#### MANGO

#### Visual merchandiser 070801-100401

As part of the management team, I was responsible for the visuals inside the store. Prepare and take out new purchase proposals in the store and style mannequins. Responsible for achieving sales goals and making analyzes of sales. Inform the staff about trends and our campaigns. Hold meetings on upcoming trends and materials science.

#### MQ

#### Visual merchandiser 040201-070713

Responsible for shop windows and all mannequins. Responsible for the visuals in the store, prepare and take out new purchase proposals in the store. Helped to open new stores and at new openings in other stores. Inform the staff about our campaigns and trends.

#### MQ

#### Säljare 030122-040201

Responsible for complaints and returns. Buyers for accessories (scarves, scarves and belts from the brand Atlas), and for Fornarina. Managed the store's clearings (send returns and complaints back to the dealer.

# ÖVRIG UTBILDNING

**FOLKUNIVERSITET**; 2008

Drawing and kroki

#### FOLKUNIVERSITETET; 2008

Illustration

# COURS DE CIVILISATION FRANCAIS DE LA SORBONNE; 2009-2010

FRANS SCHARTAU; 2009-2010

**Business administration** 

**ENSKILDA GYMNASIET; 1998-2000** 

Socio-economic program

# **REFERENCES**

Given at request